<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>My New Hugo Site</title>
    <link>http://example.org/</link>
    <description>Recent content on My New Hugo Site</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Kaulu</title>
      <link>http://example.org/kaulu/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 Jan 2023 15:55:07 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/kaulu/</guid>
      <description>logoKaulu (kah-oo-loo) is a Hawaiian word for a mythological trickster god. The search engine&amp;rsquo;s borrows its fun (with less mischief) sounding name.
Demonstration notes:
 The local search functionality is handled using Lucene. The web search functionality is handled using a Google API. To run/host the local search component, one may install and set up Apache Tomcat and drag the &amp;ldquo;jsp&amp;rdquo; folder into Tomcat&amp;rsquo;s &amp;ldquo;webapps&amp;rdquo; directory and access http://localhost:8080/jsp (8080 by default) in a web browser while Tomcat is running.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Midterm Outline</title>
      <link>http://example.org/midtermoutline/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 06 Mar 2022 03:14:59 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/midtermoutline/</guid>
      <description>Know the principles of Object Oriented programming (inheritance, encapsulation etc.)
Use All to Achieve OO:
 Inheritance: Is an ability to inherit. Function implementations (behaviors) by a subclass from a super class. Main benefit is software reuse. &amp;ldquo;No silver bullet&amp;rdquo;. Drawback: class hierarchy. Polymorphism: Is an ability to provide multiple implementations for a single function declaration. Simplifies code. Complicates testing. Superclass shape example: We need to have an array of shapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAST: A College Basketball Metric</title>
      <link>http://example.org/fast/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 31 Jan 2022 19:30:01 -0600</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://example.org/fast/</guid>
      <description>FAST stands for:
 Free throws Age Steals Turnovers  FAST is yet another one-number-metric to forecast a college basketball player&amp;rsquo;s pro potential&amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
